

Contact

E-mail:

konrad.lewandowski92@gmail.com

GitHub:

https://github.com/KonradLewandowski

Phone:

+48 666 960 130

Date of birth:

04.11.1992

City: **Gdansk**

Proficient:

JavaScript | Node | Express | SASS | HTML&CSS

Familiar:

React | Hooks | TypeScript | Git | MongoDB | PostrgeSQL | Gulp | Pug.js

Basic knowledge of:

Redux | Firebase

Languages

English - **B2** Polish - **native**

Konrad Lewandowski

I am a former soldier with a seven year experience in military service. Over the years I have acquired many traits that have shaped me to be a resilient, hard working and reliable person. Immunity to stress, determination in goal achievement, professionalism and availability are only few of my assets. For the past year I have focused on obtaining and expanding my skills in the field of web development. Frontend, backend, data bases and external API's are some of the technologies I have made myself familiar with. I would gladly join a team of developers, from whom I can learn and further expand my knowledge while working to achieve common objectives.

My projects(*programming experience*):

Portfolio website

A fully responsive one-page layout portfolio, with a simple and clean design.

Used technologies: React | TypeScript | Styled-components

Links: <u>Live Demo</u> | <u>YouTube</u>

Recipes

An application, that utilizes a Rest API, where you can search with over a million recipes and create your own.

Used technologies: HTML&CSS | JavaScript | API | Parcel

Links: <u>Live Demo</u> | <u>YouTube</u>

Calories calculator

A fully functional fullstack web application, which can create a new user, log in and log out with the JWT authentication. Resetting the password via a link sent by email. Adding a new product and searching an existing in the database. Manipulating user data. Store user's data on the server.

Used technologies: HTML&CSS | JavaScript | Pug.js | Node | Express

| MongoDB | Mongoose | Nodemailer | Parcel

Links: <u>Live Demo</u> | <u>YouTube</u>

Map Workout

A little application, that uses OpenStreetMap API.

Used technologies: HTML&CSS | JavaScript | API | Leaflet

Links: <u>Live Demo</u> | <u>YouTube</u>

Additional courses

- "Node.js, Express, MongoDB & More 2022" Udemy
- "The Complete JavaScript Course 2022" Udemy
- "Programowanie w JavaScript od Zera do Mastera" Udemy
- "Complete React Developer in 2022 (w/Redux, Hooks, GraphQL)" -Udemy(in progress)

Work experience

07.2015 – 06.2022 [7 years]

Professional soldier / 25th air cavalry brigade / Tomaszow Mazowiecki

- Availability and flexibility
- Dutiful approach to assigned tasks
- Supervision and guidance of younger members of the team
- Planning, organizing and performing group operations

07.2013 – 12.2014 [1 year 6 months]

Production line operator / Uzdrowisko Wieniec / Wieniec-Zdrój

- Maintenance on the production line
- Machines configuration

Education

09.2008 – 06.2012 ZSM Jozef Pilsudski in Radziejow **IT technician**

Hobby

- Parachuting
- Astrophysics

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realizing the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).